[
    {
        "title": "Pardon"
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "All the teachers in the pub, Passin’ round the ready rub",
        "answer": "Baggy Trousers Madness"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "You said that you’d never been, but all the things that you’ve seen, slowly fade away",
        "answer": "Don’t Look Back in Anger Oasis"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "I’m the trouble starter, Punkin instigator, I’m the fear addicted, Danger illustrated",
        "answer": "Firestarter The Prodigy"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "You think you’ve lost your love Well I saw her yesterday",
        "answer": "She Loves You The Beatles"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Jesus loves you more than you would know, wo, wo, wo",
        "answer": "Mrs. Robinson Simon and Garfunkel"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Maybe I’m foolin Maybe I’m blind",
        "answer": "Human Rag ‘n’ Bone Man"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Stepped into a church, I passed along the way",
        "answer": "California Dreamin’ The Mamas and Papas"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "No matter what they take from me, They can’t take away my dignity",
        "answer": "The Greatest Love of All Whitney Houston"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "It felt so wrong, it felt so right, don’t mean I’m in love tonight",
        "answer": "I Kissed a Girl Katy Perry"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "I hate to turn up out of the blue uninvited",
        "answer": "Someone Like You Adele"
    }
]
